Let Hae Soo go. Now!
Wolves are known for
that all their lives they love only one she-wolf
After all, you're just an animal
Out!
Project coordinator and song translator: Nemie
Make a choice
Hae Soo
or a dead emperor?
Translators: Nemie, Kaia
Beta editor and typesetter: Nemie
Hail the new emperor
Long live... Long live...
Long live the emperor
Episode 15
Chi Mon
Empress Yu said I should be glad she had a miscarriage
Choi Chi Mon
Wang So
Crown Prince Mu
I was looking forward to the arrival of my little brother
It would be better if instead of me, a man with a meager pedigree,
Tae became crown prince
Don't say that!
I told you that you were born under the star of the emperor in the constellation Hongwon!
Is it true?
Of course
That's just...
Mu...
What... if...
Is your life not that long?
What do you say?
What difference does it make if so?
Much more important is who I will spend my last days with
Brother, I also want to become an emperor
Of course you will too
Our prince Wang So was also born under the emperor's star
Really, Chi Mon?
So, will I also become an emperor?
Hooray! I will become an emperor!
Come on! You should call me "Your Majesty"
Yes, Your Majesty.
Forgive us, Your Majesty
He's the emperor
This man
emperor of our nation
Are you going to leave it like this?
Brother...
Forget everything
Rest in peace
Everything happened
because of me
I'm sorry
So...
Where are you going, brother?
Get out of my way
The new emperor ordered to convey
If Senior Lady Hae Soo leaves Damiwon,
It will be announced throughout Koryo that she poisoned the emperor.
Then she won't run far
Residence of the 10th Prince
Wang Gue, grandfather of the 10th Prince
Scoundrels!
We caught Wang Gyu, but didn't find the 10th Prince
Wang Sik Ryom
We have to grab him
Find him. Fast!
Eat!
Let go. Let go, scoundrels!
Why is the Emperor doing this to me?
Let me see him!
Your Majesty! Your Majesty!
Your Majesty!
Park Sul Hee will be exiled
Let's say that Wang Gue planned
high treason and killed Park Sul-hee
Well done
You treated Brother Mu well
And thanks for telling me to use Hae Soo to get to Seo
Now I believe that you are on my side
Without you, uncle, Uk would not have come over to my side
Shouldn't you bow to the emperor?
Greetings, Your Majesty
Long live the emperor
Eun and his wife ran away
To carry out Wang Gu's rebellion,
we have to catch Eun
Need to kill him
Don't worry
Do you have a dog that can catch them?
What's wrong with my grandson?
Let my Eun live, please!
I knew this day would come
You've been a perfect child since birth
I foresaw that you would bring me great fame
Our Emperor
Congratulations on being named Empress Dowager
Take care of the other princes quickly
This is the only way order will be restored in the palace.
- Also...
- I will take care of political affairs
Koryo is now in our hands
You should live your life enjoying the beautiful things that life offers you.
Yo...
Hurry up
Show your manners to the Emperor!
Don't be so heartless
I'm alive thanks to him
You... held back when you wanted to stab me
Letting doubts get in the way
If you feel regret, I can finish what I started
You!
Wang Gu tried to put the 10th prince on the throne,
he was sentenced to death
Catch the Prince
If you catch me, you can kill me on the spot.
Was the last emperor not enough?
I won't do this
Won't you do it?
This is the emperor's order
Then Baek Ah, Choi Chi Mon
and even Hae Soo
All those whom you consider to be your people,
will be safe
After all, you have already become a dog that will run after our relatives
I asked you not to keep him around! Get rid of him!
It's a lot of fun to tame him, so why?
Thinking of pitying me?
Is he eyeing me?
What kind of arrogance is this?
Wang Gu and his family were executed
The Emperor ordered me to find Eun and his wife
He didn't order them killed, did he?
Listen to me carefully, your highness
Emperor Taejo and I have had a strong bond since the founding of Goryeo.
We fought to the death and I remain loyal to him
But it's wrong
Don't hurt my daughter
If my daughter gets caught up in a fight between brothers,
I, Park Soo Kyung, will not sit idly by
I'm fine
What about you?
Nothing happened to you, did it?
It's true that the emperor died due to mercury poisoning
Until we know who's behind this, don't trust anyone
I'll leave the palace for a while
I'm afraid to leave you alone
Stay as far away from the Emperor and Empress as possible
If anything happens, go straight to Choi Chi Mon
Where are you going?
The Emperor wants me to catch the criminal who committed treason
Was he blackmailing you with me again?
I'll figure it out
Only you and I were next to the emperor
Is it the water or the medicinal herbs...
No one else touched them, so why?
Mercury?
It's not me
It's true
Did you think that I suspect you?
You have to be careful too
The 3rd Prince has always been a scary person
The 10th Prince's family is accused of treason
His mother and relatives...
they were all executed
What?
And the prince? What's wrong with him?
I'll leave the palace for a while
I'm afraid to leave you alone
The Emperor wants me to catch the criminal who committed treason
So, the person the 4th prince must catch...
Madam? Madam?
Su, it's me
The new emperor won't know if we hide here
The prince said we can trust you
Don't learn anything
Otherwise you will die
Ay, stop it
Anyway, Su, don't worry.
We will remain here until the ship departs.
Where will you sail?
- We...
- Enough!
You don't need to know.
Just make sure we don't get caught
Don't tell anyone about us
Okay, I'll be very careful
But wouldn't it be better to get help from the brothers?
Yes, from Uka
Or from Baek Ah and Jeong?
It can't be that they won't help me
- Even So was at my birthday
- No!
Because...
The 4th prince is looking for you now
We can't tell anyone
After all, it is unknown when everything will be revealed
Let's take a wrong step and that's it
I understand
By the way, Su
What happened to my mom and aunt?
I don't know
I don't know what's going on outside of Damiwon
It bothers me that I couldn't take them with me.
I hope they were able to escape
I thought you were a simple gisaeng
who wanted to avenge her parents
And you were the princess of Hubaekje
You hid a lot from me
I think this could be used against you, Your Majesty.
Please allow the Hupaekje people to occupy the southern territories
Let them till the land
for three years without paying tribute
Liberate those who were forcibly made slaves
Restore law-abiding citizens to their status
And let them till the land
You tried to kill the emperor
Why should I trust you?
If my people are hungry,
revenge means nothing to me
If you help them survive,
the people of Hupakje recognize you as emperor
They will become your loyal subjects
Yes...
But no matter how much I think about it,
I feel like I'm going to lose from this
I have a tempting offer
I heard the 4th prince, this dog will try to kill his brother
Shut up! So you can get into trouble
Well, I don’t believe that the carefree 10th prince was able to organize high treason
The 4th Prince behaves like the Emperor's dog
He seems to like it.
You must know something
Just eat, eat
I found a ship, sailing in 5 days
- Where from?
- This...
Four different ships depart on the same day
Not sure which one they'll take
You're not seriously going to catch Eun, are you?
Don't you trust me?
I don't trust the 3rd brother
This man became an emperor by manipulating people and exploiting their weaknesses
His future looks bleak
Find out if Eun contacted anyone
To Jeong, for example
Perhaps due to the fact that Uka had common affairs with the 3rd brother,
they say he never went anywhere
Who would have thought that he would return alive?
Woo Hee
Long time no see
Yes. Baek Ah told me that you came back
Hae Soo would be glad to see you
Maybe I'll meet her soon
I'm going back to the gisaeng house
Gisaeng house?
You didn't say that!
How long can I depend on you?
I won't be a gisaeng, I just want to learn how to dance
Don't worry so much
It's late, where are you going?
And you're really interested in me
It feels like you are behind everything
I was wondering if you visited it again
What made you think that?
The late emperor was addicted to mercury for at least two years
It seemed that Vaughn was the most suitable for the role of suspect,
but everything was too perfectly planned
This doesn't sound like Vaughn.
But if it's you...
It's strange that the emperor left you alone
Such a person would have gotten rid of you long ago
You got rid of the 10th Prince's family
and from one clan from Songak
I wonder who could do it
except for such a smart person like you
You were always suspicious of me
You
really led our brother to death?
What about you?
Will you become a dog and kill Eun?
We both spin to survive
This is the fate of the prince who did not become emperor
To defend yourself, you must submit
I don't know what made you change
I didn't poison the late emperor
Is this answer enough?
Why did you put mercury in the emperor's bath?
I didn't do that
Will you confess when they start torturing you?
Then
I would say that you ordered me to do this
They ordered to do this because they wanted to get the throne
I'll say so even if I die
And you really are amazing
I guess you've always been like this
funny
I won't get rid of you
You are the best bait
which I can control my brothers
Please
tell me who put mercury in the water
Do you think I know who did this?
Even if I find out, I won't be able to tell anyone about it.
If you say that I killed the emperor, that will be the end for me.
So I'd like to know
Who was it?
Your Majesty!
The 8th Prince has come to see you
How did he come so on time?
What?
Greetings, Your Majesty
I have a question for you.
It's good that you came
Hae Soo is dying of curiosity
Who put mercury in the water of the late emperor?
I believe he died due to illness
Isn't that right?
Yes, yes
He died due to illness
I heard you saw what happened to the late emperor
It must be terrible
He was my big brother
The man who caused him to die so horribly...
Who was it?
Your Highness,
You have nothing to do with this, do you?
I didn't raise my son to be a traitor
This is such a humiliation on your part!
I must become a traitor
to protect you and our family!
Is it because of Hae Soo?
I'm asking if Hae Soo had any
attitude towards the decisions you made?
Yes. I thought about her
It's because of her
Su said...
I tried to have everything and it was wrong. But why?
I wanted to save my family and my heart
What's the big deal?
Mother, you told me to live correctly.
I did as you told
Why am I still alone?
Uk...
I have already started my journey
I will follow it and achieve what I want
No more being a fool and losing what I want
I didn't do anything wrong
Su!
I heard the emperor called you to his chambers
I was afraid that something happened to you
I don't think he's going to kill me or banish me
He wants to use you as bait to control me
Nothing
Even so, the main thing is that you are safe
What you were talking about earlier
What will happen to the people you are looking for?
In truth...
I'm looking for Eun
The Emperor wants to find him and kill him
But I have to do my best
to help him escape
Yes
Don't worry, I'll find him
Chi Mon!
The star of the 10th prince shines over the palace
You should look again
I've already looked everywhere
And I went to Damiwon, but Eun wasn’t there
This can't happen
How much can I trust you in times like these?
Did you know that Mu would die like this?
Did you know that the 3rd brother would become emperor?
Can you imagine what it's like to know but just observe?
This is the punishment for those who read Heaven
However, even I was surprised by the appearance of the 3rd prince
He was born under the star of one who would commit treason, no more
But something has completely changed
The course of events has gone astray
What changes led to the 3rd prince becoming emperor?
Curious
Beware the 4th Prince
4th Prince...
Beware of him
Brother?
That's what Hae Soo told me
"Beware the 4th Prince"
She told me not to try to stop him.
Everything is as she said
He takes everything
No matter what I do...
he takes it away
Why?
What should I do?
Where is Court Lady He?
Sorry
Hey you
Do you know where Court Lady He is?
Stop
What kind of terrible manners are these?
Sorry
Daughter-in-law?
It's you, right?
It's you
We must leave the palace
to get to the ship
Are you kidding? There are no other doors here
North, south, west, east. There are no easy ways
There are even more guards here now than when we entered.
Yo seized the throne, and now he is afraid of getting hit
I'm ashamed that he is my brother
If only we had a Chi Mon flying machine
Or a hole in the ground
Hole? There is one
There is a way out!
Su!
I would like to say goodbye to my father
Do you think I can contact him through Choi Chi Mon?
It's dangerous
The astronomer is also close to the 4th prince
I've already thought about this
Why don't you trust the 4th prince?
You have a special relationship
I have my reasons
If you're doing this because of us, I'm grateful.
Still, I think it's wrong
I know there are bad rumors surrounding the 4th Prince
But he is not the one who can grab a person for no reason
Unless you had a bad experience yourself
But how can you not trust the person you like?
You're right
You're right, madam
I was so stupid. I have never tried to verify anything from personal experience.
I'll pay a visit to the astronomer
Astronomer?
Why do you carry a hairpin with you?
Just like that
But you must definitely return it
She doesn't look new
Does it belong to your beloved?
I thought you were only interested in fights
Curious who she is
The one who put her life on the line for me
She even covered me with her body to save me
Fuck off! Get out, you idiots!
What are you staring at? If you come closer, you're screwed!
Fuck off! Get out of here!
I remember in windless silence
And I smile because I love the sunshine...
One day I saw her sing
Then I realized
I wanted her to sing just for me someday
It all started with such desires
Do these feelings mean
that you like someone?
Exactly these!
I've been through it, I know
Did you pass?
When my elder sister was chosen as the future wife of the emperor,
all the girls from influential clans played with her
Even then I felt much more comfortable in my armor
For other children, I was like from another world
I like to fight on the field
Don't cry
Don't like this flower ring?
This is weird
All pretty girls love flower rings
You'll love them too, right?
If you love someone for real, you will never confuse this feeling
Don't worry about it and go for it
I will support you
My first love became the only and true one
Since I will share my luck with you,
and your love will be mutual, your highness
Fai-ting!
Greetings, Your Majesty
Sorry for coming so late
Please accept my congratulations
I was just about to call you
I have news about your marriage
I will send you to the Khitans
What?
The former emperor promised them Princess Gyeong-hwa
And then he married So
So I promised that I would send them a bride,
which will have the same high status
Congratulations on your wedding, Yong Hwa
Why is everyone who sits on this throne threatening to marry me?
It doesn't matter if it's the person who gave birth to me or who grew up with me.
You're all the same
You think there is no better way to control a woman
You disappointed me
You're not so greedy as to want to become an empress, are you?
Your brother betrayed me and you were on his side
I can't
to have such relatives in your home
Plus, I have someone in mind
Without Su
there is no future for me
I'm nothing without her
It's so boring here
From a young age I ran around the palace
And now I can’t leave these chambers anywhere?
At least you can go out
How many days have passed?
Would you like to take a bath?
Hae Soo doesn't allow the court ladies into the bathhouse at night, so everything will be fine
How do you like it?
Wow! How great!
Like real!
Okay, I'll show you all my skills
Attention, march!
Yes! I won!
Did you see it? I won again!
Give me your hand here
My hand already hurts a lot from hitting you.
Why does it hurt so much?
Oh yes
I was going to give this to you and forgot
You...
Did you remember to take this in all this chaos?
This is your favorite thing
Your slingshot
What kind of prince am I?
I would like to open the biggest new items store in Songak
This was my dream
You can do it
We can go to Tamra and you can open your own shop, Your Highness
And I will teach martial arts
What do you think?
I didn't forget to take this thing
Yes
I'm sure Hae Soo will like it
This is for you
Yong Hwa asked what kind of girl doesn't have a bag of incense
You're putting your husband in an awkward position.
Don't you like it?
This is weird
They say all the pretty girls love it
All pretty girls love flower rings
I'm not saying you're beautiful
It's just... lately...
you don't look that bad
I probably have problems with my eyes
Maybe I couldn’t say then
I kept everything a secret, I'm like this
How did it all start and when did it begin?
I understand what you want to say
It's so hard to remember, but now I'm with you
Even pumpkin flowers -
these are also flowers
Do you think the same as me, I wonder?
I want two sons and two daughters
This is the only thing that worries me now
And nothing else!
This all looks so much like love, since I didn’t know
Will a kiss make me pregnant?
Now throw away your worries and hug
If the heart is beating, it's love, yes
I should have been nice and lived like that from the start
Then just admit it to me
Let's go inside
You'll freeze to death before the Emperor catches us.
All the time we were far away
Wait! Am I already expecting a baby?
I want to love you so much
Hold on
Should I confess to heaven that I love him?
You are my secret love
I love it!
This all looks so much like love, since I didn’t know
Now throw away your worries and hug
If the heart is beating, it's love, yes
Then just admit it to me
What is there for you
just me
Lady, there must have been a ghost here
I'm sure I cleaned here before I went to bed.
Was someone here?
I made them
I thought I could decorate Damiwon with them
Clear
How did he make them?
Hello
I'll prepare the maids
who will serve you
I came to talk to you
Yes
This way please
Leave So
I know what you did to Uk
I know you didn't tell So about this and now he's bewitched by you
I don't want to see anything like this anymore
misbehavior, so leave him
Then I won't create problems either
Do you want to get married and leave the palace?
I'll do it for you
I can marry you into a family that is almost on the same level as the imperial one.
Marriage may be your goal, Your Highness, but not mine.
Thanks to me he is happy
Next to him I feel important, that's why I want to marry him
If he's still determined,
I have no reason to cheat on myself
I won't leave him
Now I know exactly why I always hated you
For you feelings and marriage -
these are just stupid games
And life and death depend on them for me
Don't be so sure that you won't change
No one says that in the palace
You'll regret it
I promise I'll make you regret it
General Park Soo-kyung and astronomer Choi Chi-mon
They have military and religious power and support Wang So
You must get rid of the 4th prince quickly
Not long ago we were planning Wang Gu's rebellion
Besides, So and I have the same mother.
To attack him, you need to choose the right time
Then you should separate Park Soo Kyung and Choi Chi Mon
What is this?!
I want to make things easier for you two
- What?
- In return,
if my plan doesn't work,
cancel my marriage with the Khitan
I was told that you know where Eun is
Where is he?
Senior court lady Hae Soo hid Eun and his wife in Damiwon
How did you know?
Did you see it yourself?
Even as a child, Eun knew how to fold things from canvases
Dogs, birds
And he made ships out of paper
Damiwon is teeming with Eun's crafts
I'm sure
Follow this path to the cave, Jeong will be waiting outside
He will help you get to the ship safely
This is dried meat
Just in case
Thank you
big
Su, see you when I get back
Yes I'll be waiting
By the way, what about your father?
I left a letter.
I'm sure he will meet you on the way
Let's go
Run! Palace guards are everywhere!
- Jeong...
- I'll stop them, run!
You too!
We must arrest the 10th prince. Find him!
Eat!
Take the prince another way
What?
They can't kill me because of my father
They have come for you, Your Highness
You can't
Let's go together
I'll be there soon
I promise
I trust you
Like your wife said, we need to run
I can't. I can't hide behind my wife
Your Highness!
What can I do?
I'm the best for her
I'm all she has
As if a free wind will carry you away
Thanks for watching with us!
Release group MANIA
http://doramamania.mybb.ru
http://vk.com/doramamania
I kept looking for the way to you, but I never found it
Scarlet Hearts: Ryeo
Why are you whining about the death of a couple of useless slaves?!
I couldn’t catch the fate that was moving away from me
I'll kill him
The inhumanity of brothers who want to kill each other...
I started it, I will finish it
So I'll let you go completely
Jeong wants to take the throne?
You haven't forgotten me, have you?
Looking at your footprints when you leave me
Hae Soo is still with him
I told you you couldn't trust him when he said he'd be your dog.
Now I couldn’t hold back my tears
I'll be the dog that ends his life
I will become the Emperor of Goryeo